Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: By-Laws, 1942; Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Blast - published by Local 12 IUMSWA, 1950; Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Suggestions for brief in arbitration case, 1955; Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Jobs Now: ship employment program sabotaged, group in National Office fiddles while your jobs go up in smoke (newspaper), Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Facts you should know., 1942; Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Dedication Ceremonies, 1953; Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
    Notes: program
  - Item 7: Correspondence, Publication (Box 252, Folder 2)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A plan of group insurance, 1944; Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A program for veterans, 1943; Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Here are the dollars and sense of American shipping, Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Nation that invented the steamship must now use it, Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
    Notes: Report to the American People by John Green, President, the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), CIO. second copy
  - Item 5: Accounting Manual, Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Johnny Green Stabilizer, 1943; Publication (Box 252, Folder 3)
    Author: Frank Rahill
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Organization Notes, 1946; Publication (Box 252, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 5-7, 9-10 (1946)
  - Item 2: Organization Notes, 1945; Publication (Box 252, Folder 4)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Data which can be used by Local Unions in negotiation of Health and Welfare Benefit Programs, 1947; Publication (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Digest of findings of compilation of data on payment for unworked holidays, 1945; Publication (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Pension and insurance plans of Bethlehem Steel Company, 1955; Publication (Box 252, Folder 5)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Financial status of the. In the United States as of January, 1944, Publication (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Ships for victory, 1942; Publication (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Story of the Industrial Union, 1941; Publication (Box 252, Folder 6)
    Notes: Reprinted from August, 1941 issue, Labor Information Bulletin, US Dept. of Labor. second copy
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: IUMSWA makes each $1.25 count, 1946; Publication (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Leadership Training Program: Conference & Structure and Function of the IUMSWA, Publication (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Accounting Manual, Publication (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Report of the General Executive Board to the Fourth National Policy Conference, 1955; Publication (Box 252, Folder 7)
- Pacific American Ship-owners Association; Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast, Publication (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Before the war shipping panel, National War Labor Board: in the matter of Pacific American Ship-owners Association, and Marine Cooks & Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast: Appendix, Union exhibits, 1944; Publication (Box 253, Folder 1)
- National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, Publication (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Parliamentary procedure at a glance, 1948; Publication (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Shipping Rules adopted by unanimous vote at the second biennial convention, 1947; Publication (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: MCS 1901-1951 Half Century of Progress -, Publication (Box 253, Folder 2)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: MEBA pension trust, 1963; Publication (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: MEBA pension trust, 1966; Publication (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: MEBA Health and Welfare Plan Welfare Fund, 1977; Publication (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: U.S. Flag Shipping, How the industry is working toward total service - together, 1975; Publication (Box 253, Folder 3)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: MEBA pension trust - pension fund, 1977; Publication (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: MEBA, Atlantic - Gulf - Pacific Coasts Vacation Plan, 1977; Publication (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: MEBA Health and Welfare Plan MEBA Welfare Fund, 1971; Publication (Box 253, Folder 4)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.). Local 101 (Great Lakes District), Publication (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Marine Engineer, 1959; Publication (Box 253, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.4-9
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Know your rights: clarification and interpretations of collective bargaining agreements, Pension and Welfare Plan, Vacation Plan, Maintenance and Cure, Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: MEBA News - Special Strike Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct. 5, 1946
  - Item 3: MEBA News - Special Strike Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct. 12, 1946
  - Item 4: MEBA News - Special Strike Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1, no. 1
  - Item 5: MEBA News letter, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.23
  - Item 6: MEBA News letter, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.37
  - Item 7: MEBA News letter, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.33
  - Item 8: MEBA new wage scale for dry cargo, 1956; Publication (Box 253, Folder 6)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Minimum wage scale, crew list, rules and regulations governing employment of Engineers for Trans-Atlantic, Atlantic and Gulf Coast's Service, 1918; Publication (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Minimum wage scale crew list rules and regulations governing employment of Engineers on ships engaged in Atlantic Gulf Coast's Service, 1916; Publication (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The American Marine Engineer, 1946; Publication (Box 253, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 39, no.2
  - Item 4: Delegates instructions, 1933; Publication (Box 253, Folder 7)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Marine Engineering., 1976; Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: MEBA - Diagnostic Centers: A complete health check-up. Why is it important to you?, 1967; Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1964; Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The big issue is jobs, 1961; Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: MEBA Pension Trust, MEBA Pension Fund, 1973; Publication (Box 253, Folder 8)
- National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Worthy of our heritage, 1975; Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
    Notes: Brief history of America's oldest Maritime Union, published in commemoration of the centennial anniversary, Marine Engineers Beneficial Association. 1875-1975
  - Item 2: American Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
    Notes: Mar-70
  - Item 3: Jimmy Carter on the U.S. Flag Merchant Marine, 1976; Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
    Author: Jimmy Carter
  - Item 4: Tomorrow we embark upon the boundless sea, 1976; Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Tomorrow we embark upon the boundless sea, Publication (Box 253, Folder 9)
- Professional Air Traffic controllers Organization (PATCO), Publication (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: PATCO - Anniversary Issue, 1979-1980 (Box 253, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.5, no.1; vol. 3, no.8; vol. 4, no. 1
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Assoc., Publication (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Financial report, 1948; Publication (Box 253, Folder 11)
- Pacific Coast Marine Firemen, Oilers, Water tenders and Wipers Association, Publication (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agents Conference, 1945-1946 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information on Welfare - Pension and Vacation plans, Publication (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The story of the Marine Firemen's Union, 1945; Publication (Box 254, Folder 1)
- United Merchant Marine Officers Association, Publication (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Memo about purpose of union, Publication (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: New Union set up for ship officers, 1953; Publication (Box 254, Folder 2)
- Soderberg, Bunker and Trajer, Publication (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The case of Soderberg, Bunker and Trajer, 1932; Publication (Box 254, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Marine Workers Voice, 1931; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 7 (1931)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: For want of a nail, 1947; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The union's trouble-shooters, 1944; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The struggle of the marine workers, 1930; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
    Author: N. Sparks
  - Item 6: Centralized shipping bureau, 1934; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Point Gorda strike, Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
    Author: George Clark
  - Item 8: 4 fighting years: a short history of the Marine Workers Industrial Union: a letter to ships' delegates, 1933; Publication (Box 254, Folder 4)
- United Seamen's Service, inc., Publication (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Yanks are not coming, 1940; Publication (Box 254, Folder 5)
    Author: Mike Quin
  - Item 2: The Pacific Coast maritime strike, 1937; Publication (Box 254, Folder 5)
    Author: William Schneiderman
  - Item 3: A post war service program for American merchant seamen. 1. The situation in 1942. 2. The United Seamen's Service. 3. The post war outlook, 1945; Publication (Box 254, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pilot (A National Paper for Maritime Workers), 1947; Publication (Box 255, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb. 6, 1947
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: NMU employment security plan, 1957; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: NMU Welfare Plan, description of major medical benefits, Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
    Notes: memo
  - Item 3: NMU security: the NMU Welfare Plan, the NMU Employment Security Plan, the NMU Pension Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: NMU Great Lakes welfare and pension plan, 1959; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: NMU welfare plan, Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: NMU Pension Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: NMU Pension Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: NMU Pension and Welfare Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: NMU Pension and Welfare Plan: 2 year report, January 1, 1951 to December 31, 1952, 1953; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: NMU Pension Plan, NMU Welfare Plan, NMU Employment Security Plan: benefits effective, June 16, 1958, Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: NMU welfare plan, 1969; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Financial problems: making ends meet, 1958; Publication (Box 255, Folder 2)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Biographical notes on Shannon J. Wall, President, National maritime Union of America, 1973; Publication (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Biographical notes on Mel Barisic, Acting Secretary-Treasurer of the National Maritime Union of America, Publication (Box 255, Folder 3)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Call, 1966; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1966 - (Aug.-Sept.)
  - Item 2: The Call, 1967; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1967 - (Mar.)
  - Item 3: The Call, 1968; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1968 - (Feb.-Aug., Nov.- Dec.)
  - Item 4: The Call, 1969; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1969 - (Jan.-Feb., Apr., July, Nov.)
  - Item 5: The Call, 1969; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1969 Contract Issue
  - Item 6: The Call, 1970; Publication (Box 255, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1970 - (Jan., July)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Continued "20" Years of progress, 1958; Publication (Box 255, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: In the United States Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit: National Labor Relations Board, Petitioner, v. National Maritime Union of America, affiliated with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, and Joseph Curran, Jack Lawrence, Josh Lawrence, C, 1948; Publication (Box 255, Folder 6)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Which way for MEBA?, Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Thoughts for MEBA members, Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: President's Report - Fourteenth National Convention, 1966; Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Our visit to the U.S.S.R.: a report to the membership of the National Maritime Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1959; Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
    Author: Joseph Curran
  - Item 5: The membership wins again: a record of recent events in the National Maritime Union, 1937; Publication (Box 255, Folder 7)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: National Deep Sea Shipping Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Who's guilty? A record of certain activities of the United States Bureau of Marine Inspection and Navigation, with regard to safety- at-sea and the collective bargaining rights of seamen., 1940; Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Labor spies in the NMU, 1947; Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: From kitchen to congress, 1944; Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Heroes today, tramps tomorrow?, 1944; Publication (Box 255, Folder 8)
    Author: William Gropper
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1942; Publication (Box 255, Folder 9)
    Notes: article. March 20, 1942
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1942; Publication (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Labor spies in the NMU, 1947; Publication (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Do you know that [your union has practically doubled the wages of seamen in the last ten years?], 1942; Publication (Box 255, Folder 9)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: This man can wreck the union, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Who is the pay-off man for the ship-owners?, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: D-day was the supreme test, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Why a strike?, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: What time is it, America?, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Stop lynchings and lynch-murder, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Lakes seamen, 40 hr. week, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: The Conspiracy against the Maritime Unions, 1948; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Memorandum of National Maritime Union of America - Re: Proposed amendment to war risk insurance policy, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: The Chips are down for June 15th, 1947; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Heroes in Dungarees: the story of the contribution of American Merchant Seamen to the war effort!, Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Why a Great Lakes Shipping Strike - August 15th, 1946; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Pension wheel - NMU Pension Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Standard Fruit & Steamship Co., Steamship Dept. - manual of instruction, 1941; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
    Notes: pamphlet
  - Item 15: The NMU fights Jim Crow, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Listen brothers!, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: The check off, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
    Author: Harold Price
  - Item 18: Hold that meeting!, 1944; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Democracy on U.S. ships, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: The NMU: what it is, what it does, 1943; Publication (Box 255, Folder 10)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: From kitchen to congress, 1944; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Heroes today, tramps tomorrow?, 1944; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: from the men who man the ships to the men who man the guns, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Merchant seamen and the law, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
    Author: William L. Standard
  - Item 5: Know the score: on Seamen's conditions before the NMU, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A weather eye to the future: NMU federal credit union, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Welcome brother, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The river rat murder case: the NMU post-war program, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
    Author: Aleine Austin
  - Item 9: Profit vs. pay: an address by Lee Pressman delivered at fifth convention of the National Maritime Union, CIO, New York City, July 6, 1945, Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
    Author: Lee Pressman
  - Item 10: Take the helm, 1944; Publication (Box 256, Folder 1)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Steering to victory, Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Joint Termination regulation (War Dept., Navy Dept.), 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
    Notes: Revision no. 4, 11 Oct. 1945
  - Item 3: High Wages for Merchant Seamen?, Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: D-Day was the supreme test, Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Antenna, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1. published monthly by Atlantic District Local 2
  - Item 6: Peacetime program of the Natl. Maritime Union, 1945; Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Post-war shipping: resolution adopted by the National Council of the National Maritime Union, July, 1944, Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The check off, 1943; Publication (Box 256, Folder 2)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report to the membership, 1946; Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
    Notes: By Joseph Curran, from July 5 issue of The Pilot. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Strike support rules, 1946; Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Longshoremen: NMU thanks you for your support, 1946; Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Battle stations for peace, Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Overtime pay for pursers, Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Oigan comapaneros, Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: an NMU label on every lakes vessel, Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: When our Seamen ship out, 1946; Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Equality for all: the stand of the NMU on discrimination, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 3)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Songs for Seamen, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: How our Seamen bounced the commies, 1948; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
    Author: Donal Robinson
  - Item 3: Money Lost!, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: the NMU trade union school pays off, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: It's your union, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Ships committee is the heart of the union, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: a good union man is a good seaman, know your job and do it!, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: A clean ship, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: NMU on higher wages, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Calling all ships, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: NMU members this is your education program, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Thats the ticket, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Por atras, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Democracy for all: NMU manual on parliamentary procedure for ship and shore meetings, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: N.M.U. manual: political action., 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: In the back: NMU analysis of the Taft-Hartley law, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Building NMU: a handbook for ship organizers, deep sea, Great Lakes, rivers, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Taft-Hartley "Union shop" means open shop for seamen!: report to National Council, Apr. 21, 1948, Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Pork chops and politics, 1943; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: A handbook on Seamen's Unemployment Insurance // Manual de Seguro Paramarinos Desempleados, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 4)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Manual of organization for ship organizers on the Great Lakes, 1943; Publication (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A building program to meet our needs / National Maritime Union of America, 1956; Publication (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: El Corazon de la Union, 1947; Publication (Box 256, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Financial report, 1947-1949 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    Notes: July 1, 1947-June 30, 1949
  - Item 2: Financial report, 1955-1957 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    Notes: July 1, 1955-June 30, 1957
  - Item 3: Financial report, 1957; Publication (Box 256, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1-June 30, 1957